{
"question": "姉",
"answer": "あね"
},
{
"question": "百",
"answer": "ひゃく"
},
{
"question": "在る",
"answer": "ある"
},
{
"question": "其の",
"answer": "その"
},
{
"question": "言う",
"answer": "いう"
},
{
"question": "出来る",
"answer": "できる"
},
{
"question": "良い",
"answer": "よい"
},
{
"question": "下さい",
"answer": "ください"
},
{
"question": "見る",
"answer": "みる"
},
{
"question": "此の",
"answer": "この"
},
{
"question": "自分",
"answer": "じぶん"
},
{
"question": "知る",
"answer": "しる"
},
{
"question": "持つ",
"answer": "もつ"
},
{
"question": "何",
"answer": "なに"
},
{
"question": "車",
"answer": "くるま"
},
{
"question": "話す",
"answer": "はなす"
},
{
"question": "今",
"answer": "いま"
},
{
"question": "今日",
"answer": "きょう"
},
{
"question": "買う",
"answer": "かう"
},
{
"question": "読む",
"answer": "よむ"
},
